The students of the mother of the mother have a big news
attached to the velvet chapter, I am definitely paying attention to the
two cups of tea on IRCTC, but if it
comes then please give me this is a bit disappointing news
because according to senior railway
officials, the railway's train
operation in cold areas may take two
more months, if according to this period, the
passenger train which you have just seen on the track may take
two more months,
according to railway sources, in the month of March,
almost by the end of the 100%
passenger train operation circle officer, it simply
means that the back side of IRCTC is done
through online ticketing, it will take some
time to return to the police force, till then the
income from the activity which is done through online
ticketing will also keep
increasing keeping in mind, it is true that the railway must
say that every month for years they have been
including both the trains and
running them as special trains, but this
indication that the earnings are less, then it was different that the earnings are
not being achieved as much as the online ticket duty, or
someone's fans seem to be very strong,
but by the end of the month, 100% train
operation will be in place, till now it is also known  The
ITGK Group
believes that the benefits of animals will be seen through online ticket sales.